<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coolderry</title>
    <description>Introducing Pearl...portable lyrics for everyone!
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 23:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 23:51:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Maintainable</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;There are always new songs to enjoy and share. Maintaining the database of songs is trouble free. Add new songs directly or import them from a USB flash drive or even from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ccli.com/&quot;&gt;CCLI Song Select&lt;/a&gt;. See the &lt;a href=&quot;https://manual.openlp.org/songs.html&quot;&gt;OpenLP Song documentation&lt;/a&gt; for an extensive list of the import options available.
This is all possible because of the broad range of features in OpenLP but does require a keyboard and mouse. The Pearl has 4 USB ports for adding input devices and removable storage.&lt;br /&gt;
Moreover, Pearl has an optional wireless keyboard touchpad which is just the right size for portability and usability.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2016 20:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/feature/2016/02/06/maintainable.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/feature/2016/02/06/maintainable.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Feature</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Convenient</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;automatic&quot;&gt;Automatic&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pearl makes lyrics presentation easy, convenient and hassle free. Pearl automatically starts once plugged in and automatically reloads the last saved set list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;wifi-hotspot&quot;&gt;WiFi Hotspot&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The device provides a WiFi Hotspot, with a unique SSID so more than one can operate in close proximity, for effortless connectivity. In particular this makes it possible to use any smart phone for selecting songs and controlling what is presented. When the Pearl is plugged into a network through the Ethernet port the device can provide wireless access for others to access the network. This means it is possible to set up a convenient guest wireless network if desired.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 20:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/feature/2016/02/05/convenient.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/feature/2016/02/05/convenient.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Feature</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Versatile</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;portable-computer&quot;&gt;Portable computer&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pearl is essentially a computer in your pocket. With the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.raspberrypi.org/&quot;&gt;Raspberry Pi&lt;/a&gt; at the heart of it the device gives you a lot of options to do more. All you need is a screen, power and an input device such as a keyboard &amp;amp; mouse to edit documents, browse the internet, play games and watch videos. For example, the device comes with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.libreoffice.org/&quot;&gt;LibreOffice suite&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.claws-mail.org/&quot;&gt;Claws Mail&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.chromium.org/&quot;&gt;Chrome browser&lt;/a&gt; installed. The list of possibilities is huge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;powerful-software&quot;&gt;Powerful software&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pearl uses the feature rich &lt;a href=&quot;https://openlp.org/&quot;&gt;OpenLP&lt;/a&gt; to manage and present song lyrics. OpenLP is free open source Church worship presentation software. Being open source also means that the developers are continuously working to improve this application, and welcome any comments or questions users may have. Although the Pearl primarily uses, and enhances, the OpenLP Songs feature, all the other features such as support for LibreOffice presentations, Bibles, Media, Custom Slides and Stage View are all there. Do check out the OpenLP website to find out how much this amazing software application in your pocket can be put to use.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2016 20:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/feature/2016/02/04/versatile.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/feature/2016/02/04/versatile.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Feature</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Easy to use</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;select-and-go&quot;&gt;Select and go:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Pearl auto starts once plugged in and will load the last saved set list. That means the songs can be selected ahead of time, saved and within minutes of getting to the venue (friend’s sitting room or hotel meeting room) everything is ready to go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;any-smartphone&quot;&gt;Any smartphone:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any smartphone with a javascript enabled browser can be used to select songs. The web application interface is so intuitive anyone can run the lyrics presentation from their smartphone. Unlikely other smartphone based lyrics presentation apps, no one has to hand over their own phone to anyone else in order to run it. What’s more, there’s nothing to install if the smartphone already has a javascript enabled web browser!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 20:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/feature/2016/02/03/easy-to-use.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/feature/2016/02/03/easy-to-use.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Feature</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connected</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;video&quot;&gt;Video:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supplied with a 1.5 metre HDMI cable and a HDMI / VGA connector the Pearl is ready to be used with the majority of televisions and projectors in homes, hotels, churches and convention centres. The audio out port can also be used to for RCA composite Audio Visual output. That means the Pearl has a video connection option for almost every popular display out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;wireless-control&quot;&gt;Wireless Control:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The selection and presentation of songs can be controlled from any smartphone. The smartphone can connect to the Pearl WiFi Access Point. Alternatively, the Pearl can plug in the an existing network through it’s Ethernet port.
The wireless keyboard &amp;amp; touchpad is a convenient option to add or import songs on the go. Although any USB or Bluetooth keyboard and mouse can be used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;usb&quot;&gt;USB:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Pearl has 4 USB ports which can be used to import songs from a USB flash drive or plug in an additional input device.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 20:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/feature/2016/02/02/connected.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/feature/2016/02/02/connected.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Feature</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Compact</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;only-9cm-x-65cm-x-25cm&quot;&gt;Only 9cm x 6.5cm x 2.5cm&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Small enough to take with you anywhere. As you can see, it easily fits in a child’s hand. Even with the supplied power adapter, compact HDMI cable and HDMI / VGA connector, the Pearl fits in any musician’s gear bag. It takes up less space than a laptop and weighs less too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;slot-slot-in-almost-anywhere&quot;&gt;Slot slot in almost anywhere&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Pearl can be discretely positioned behind, under, above or beside the TV or projector. That means it can be secured in place to. The Pearl is controlled wirelessly so no direct access is required once it is powered on.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 20:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/feature/2016/02/01/compact.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/feature/2016/02/01/compact.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Feature</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
